A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Diane Van Wie, Series 34 FA373
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1953-1973; 02; 9 document box(es)
  - Transportation Bond Issue (Box 25, Folder 590)
    State-Federal-Local participation in the five year transportation financial needs for highway, aviation and mass transportation. Statistics from the Associated Industries of New York, the Municipal Forum of New york, an essay by Leland Hazard "Welfare, Social Work, and Business Transition". Recommendations on the organization of the department of transportation, New York State Department of Public Works, June 30, 1967. A report on transportation bond issue. The highway program by category: 1967-68; 1971-72, a list of federal funds and state funds in regards to the highway program by category. Statistics for the highway program by area: 1967-68; 1971-72. A memo about which highways and roads would be completed under the new highway program. Memo on aviation and its importance. Memo on mass transportation and its economic value. A brochure "Transportation... Trends and Transition in New York State".
  - Actions for Transportation in New York State, Inc., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 591)
    Contributions as of above date.
  - Governor's "Fifteen Trips" Format, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 592)
    A memorandum describing the Governor's "Fifteen trips".
  - Up to the Minute - Headline Profiles - WCBS-NY, May 24, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 593)
    Transcript of a TV interview with Deputy Mayor Robert Price.
  - Urban Development Corporation (UDC) Program, undated (Box 25, Folder 594)
    Agenda for the briefing on Urban Development Corporation (UDC) program.
  - President Johnson's List of Urban Aid Programs - from Congressional Quarter/IV (Box 25, Folder 595)
    A list of President Johnson's Urban Aid Programs, from congressional quarterly. A memo regarding welfare costs, April 18, 1968. Charts on unemployment. A chart on Gross National Product. Charts on federal budget deficit, 1969. Charts on budget outlays, 1969. A chart on federal expenditures 1968 and 1969. Charts on consumer prices. Chart on wage increase. Chart on interest rate. Chart on U. S. balance of payments deficit. Chart on U. S. gold stock. Chart of U. S. trade surplus.
  - Urban Industrial Development Plan, undated (Box 25, Folder 596)
  - Vetoed Bills, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 597)
    A chart of cost to New York businesses of bills vetoed. Budget implications of vetoed bills - state savings.
  - Vietnam Report (Box 25, Folder 598)
    A Study of the Vietnam Conflict. Interview of Gen. Gavin by Edwin Newman. Vietnam VII - The Presidential Election, September 3, 1967.
  - Welfare, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 599)
    Newspaper clippings concerning welfare. Charts on job training.
  - What is the Relation Between Poverty and Mental Health?, undated (Box 25, Folder 600)
    A passage by Frank Riessman.
  - Why a New Correctional Institution is Needed at Stony Kill Farm, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 601)
    A memo with a list of reasons why a correctional institution is needed at Stony Kill Farm.
  - Women's Unit, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 602)
    A press release on the appointment of Kitty Carlisle Hart. A mailing list of women who are employees of newspapers and magazines.
  - Works of Art in the Executive Mansion, undated (Box 25, Folder 603)
    A list of works of art in the Executive Mansion.
  - Youth and Work Programs (Labor), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 604)
  - The Brooklyn Navy Yard - A Plan for Redevelopment, May 1968 (Box 161, Folder 4176)
- Acknowledgements of Support Gubernatorial/National, 1968-1970; 03; 10 document box(es)
  This subseries first is grouped into gubernatorial and presidential campaign letters of support and then is arranged alphabetically by state, followed by the name of the supporter.
  The letters in this subseries are copies of outgoing correspondence.
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 605)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 606)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 607)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 608)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 609)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 610)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 611)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 612)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 613)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 614)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 615)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 616)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 617)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 618)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 619)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 620)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 621)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 622)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 623)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 624)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 625)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 626)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 627)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 628)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 629)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 630)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 631)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (A-Cu), 1964-1970 (Box 26, Folder 632)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 633)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 634)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 635)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 636)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 637)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 638)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 639)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 640)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 641)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 642)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 643)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 644)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 645)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 646)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 647)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 648)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 649)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 650)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 651)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 652)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 653)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 654)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 655)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 656)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 657)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 658)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 659)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 660)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 661)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 662)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 663)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (D-Ha), 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 664)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 665)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 666)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 667)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 668)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 669)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 670)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 671)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 672)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 673)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 674)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 675)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 676)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 677)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 678)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 679)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 680)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 681)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 682)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 683)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 684)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 685)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 686)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 687)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 688)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 689)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 690)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 691)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 692)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 693)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 694)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 695)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 696)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 697)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (He-Man), 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 698)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 699)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 700)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 701)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 702)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 703)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 704)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 705)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 706)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 707)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 708)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 709)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 710)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 711)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 712)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 713)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 714)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 715)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 716)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 717)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 718)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 719)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 720)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 721)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 722)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 723)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 724)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 725)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 726)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 727)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 728)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 729)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 730)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 731)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Mc-Ru), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 732)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 733)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 734)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 735)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 736)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 737)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 738)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 739)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 740)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 741)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 742)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 743)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 744)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 745)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 746)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 747)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 748)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 749)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 750)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 751)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 752)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 753)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 754)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 755)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 756)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 757)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 758)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 759)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 760)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 761)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 762)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 763)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 764)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 765)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 766)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, Gubernatorial (Sa-Z), 1964-1970 (Box 30, Folder 767)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 768)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 769)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 770)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 771)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 772)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 773)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 774)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 775)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 776)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 777)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 778)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 779)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 780)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 781)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 782)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 783)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 784)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 785)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 786)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 787)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 788)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 789)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 790)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 791)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 792)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 793)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 794)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 795)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 796)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 797)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Alabama - Delaware), 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 798)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 799)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 800)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 801)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 802)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 803)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 804)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 805)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 806)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 807)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 808)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 809)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 810)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 811)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 812)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 813)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 814)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 815)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 816)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 817)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 818)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 819)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 820)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 821)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 822)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 823)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Florida - Maryland), 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 824)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Maryland - New Jersey), 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 825)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Maryland - New Jersey), 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 826)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Maryland - New Jersey), 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 827)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Maryland - New Jersey), 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 828)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Maryland - New Jersey), 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 829)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Maryland - New Jersey), 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 830)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Maryland - New Jersey), 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 831)
  - Acknowledgement of Support, National (Maryland - New Jersey), 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 832)